skoal.com 2010-12-30

# Skoal® Smokeless Tobacco - Privacy Policy

**Last updated on (October 31, 2008).**

General  
USSTC will not collect any personally identifiable information about you (e.g., your name, address, telephone number or email address ("personal data") through our website unless you have provided it to us voluntarily. If you do not want your personal data collected, please do not submit it to us.

Personal Data  
USSTC will not collect any personally identifiable information about you (e.g., your name, address, telephone number or email address ["personal data"]) through our website unless you have provided it to us voluntarily. If you do not want your personal data collected, please do not submit it to us.

When you do provide us with personal data, we may use that information in the following ways, unless stated otherwise: we may store and process that information to better understand your preferences and how we can improve our products and services; we (or a fulfillment house or other third party working on our behalf in connection with a promotion) may use that information to contact you; and/or we may provide other third parties working on our behalf with aggregate — but not individual — information about visitors to our sites. Neither we nor any third party working on our behalf will sell, rent or market personal data about you to another third party unless you have given us specific permission.

If you disclose personal information to us via registration in connection with a promotion that we run, we may use that personal information to contact you (e.g., if you win a contest) and disclose that information to third parties for purposes of administering the promotion (e.g., travel agencies) and required government reporting (e.g., income tax reporting).

USSTC may disclose personal information if we are required to do so by law or legal process, to law enforcement or other government authorities or if we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity, such as fraud.

Additional Information Collected Automatically  
In some cases, we may automatically (i.e., not via registration) collect technical information when you connect to our site that is not personally identifiable. Examples of this type of information include the kind of computer operating system you are using and the domain name of the website from which you linked to our site. If your IP (Internet Protocol) address is collected, we may use it, in the aggregate with other IP addresses, to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movement and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We use IP addresses on an aggregated basis to examine our traffic on our websites—not to collect or evaluate individual information.

Information Placed Automatically on Your Computer–Cookies  
When you view one of our websites, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "cookie" or similar file and can help us in many ways. For example, cookies allow us to tailor a website to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet browsers, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions. Remember though, without cookies, you may not be able to take full advantage of all our website features.

Web Beacons  
Certain pages on our site contain “web beacons” (also known as Internet tags, pixel tags and clear GIFs). These web beacons allow third parties working on our behalf to obtain information such as the IP address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the beacon appears, the URL of the page on which the beacon appears, the time the page containing the beacon was viewed, the type of browser used to view the page and the information in cookies set by the third party working on our behalf.

Links to Other Sites  
We may provide links to other websites for your convenience and information. The sites operate independently from U.S. Smokeless Tobacco Co. These sites may have their own privacy statements in place, which we strongly suggest you review if you visit any linked websites. To the extent any linked websites you visit are not corporately related to U.S. Smokeless Tobacco Co., we are not responsible for their content or any use of these sites.

How We Protect Your Information  
We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards for this website to protect against unauthorized disclosure, use, alteration or destruction of the information you provide on the site.

Your Preferences  
If you would like to have your name removed from the adult consumer mailing list, please write to U.S. Smokeless Tobacco Co. Opt Out, PO Box 29008, Miami, FL 33102-9008 or call the number that appears on the most recent piece of mail you received from U.S. Smokeless Tobacco Co.

Changes to Your Information  
If your personally identifiable information changes (e.g., you change your residence address), or if a correction is required (e.g., we do not have your correct mailing address), you may contact us through the "Contact Us" function on our website.

Changes to Privacy Policy  
We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the Privacy Policy. For material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by placing prominent notice on the website.
